https://www.rvresources.com/privacypolicy.php

Privacy Policy for RV Resources
The privacy of our visitors to rvresources.com is important to us.
At rvresources.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive
and collect when you use and visit rvresources.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.
Log Files
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer
or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited
throughout our site.
Cookies and Web Beacons
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.
We also use third party advertisements on rvresources.com to support our site. Some
of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases,
whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting
purposes (showing Florida real estate ads to someone in Florida, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing camping
ads to someone who frequents camping sites).
DoubleClick DART cookies
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving
through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you
are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific
to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about motorhomes in California, you may see California RV Dealer advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about
baseball). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT
track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical
address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting https://www.doubleclickbygoogle.com/
You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
Home
Submit a Site
RV Dealers
RV Parks
Books
Contact
The RV Directory built by RVers like you, please
contact us with any suggestions you may have or features you would like to see added.
